THEOPHILUS AYANO

A highly skilled and versatile professional with a solid background in full-stack web development and extensive experience as a sales manager. Possessing a unique blend of technical expertise and business acumen, I excel in bridging the gap between technology and commercial success. With a proven track record in both software development and sales management, I bring a valuable perspective to any organization, driving innovation and achieving tangible results.



Experience

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PHOENIX INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY 2021-PRESENT

- Develop and maintain professional and in-house web applications
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to design and implement new features.
- Work closely with project stakeholders to gather requirements and provide technical insights.
- Utilize sales experience to contribute valuable perspectives on user experience, customer engagement, and market demand, resulting in enhanced application functionality and user satisfaction.

IT CONSULTANT AND SALES MANAGER BITMAS BAKERY Ltd 2019-2021

- Advised on technology solutions to improve business processes and procedures.
- Utilize sales experience to contribute valuable perspectives on user experience, customer

FULL STACK DEVELOPER AND IT CONSULTANT ZXT TECHNOLOGY 2017-2019

- Lead end-to-end software developments, from requirements gathering and system design to coding, testing, and deployment, ensuring on-time and withinbudget project delivery
- Advised clients on emerging technologies, industry trends, and best practices, guiding them in making informed decision regarding their IT infrastructure and digital transformation strategies.



PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATIONS

- ✓ CERTIFICATE IN MANAGEMENT, NIGERIA INSTITUTE OF MANAGEMENT(NIM)
- ✓ CERTIFICATE IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING, ALX AFRICA
- ✓ CCNA1 CERTIFICATE, CISCO

- Email: kenkszii@gmail.com
- (c) Cell phone: 08066286427
- LinkedIn Profile: linkedin.com/in/kenkszii/
- Portfolio: https://www.sheyi.tech
 - Address: Kaduna, Nigeria



Relevant Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Python
- JavaScript
- ReactJs
- Flask
- Technical documentation
- Lookup portfolio for more: https://www.sheyi.tech



Education History

2021-2023 MBA (finance and investment)

Ahmadu Bello University

2013-2017 BSC(ED) Computer Science

Ahmadu Bello University

2010-2013 NCE Physics and Computer Sc.

Federal College of Education

Zaria.



Specialization

- ✓ Developer
- ✓ Graphics design
- ✓ Coach
- ✓ Entrepreneur
- √ IT Professional
- ✓ Business Manager
- ✓ Business Development
- ✓ Customer Relationship Management
- ✓ Digital Marketer



Referees

Available on request.